Ricardo Cortez



rcortez.online@gmail.com



317-512-3566



linkedin.com/in/ricky-cortez-70301921a

Summary

Experienced Sales representative with 7 years of excellent customer service in the telecom industry. Specialize with Apple products and am an approved Apple Master for the Indianapolis South. Extensive range of knowledge with communication devices from cellphones to tablets as well as Data entry and Trouble shooting.

Experience



Technical Representative

Conduent

Mar 2019 - Mar 2021 (2 years 1 month)

Led teams of sales personnel to assist customers in a variety of products ranging from handheld devices to computers.

Taught sales personnel correct ways of approaching multiple scenarios and coming out with a solution that fits the customers needs.

Able to consistently keep sales above average per quarter period of (Ranging from 78-82%).

Perfect Attendance across multiple Quarters (2019 - 2020)

Administrative Assistant

HandledNow, LLC

Oct 2017 - Oct 2018 (1 year 1 month)

Arrange, change, and create locations in the Subaru yard for incoming parts. Use various programs such as PINC and Excel to correctly coordinate their logistics yard



Salesperson

Moorehead Communications Inc

Oct 2015 - Feb 2017 (1 year 5 months)

Help Verizon customers choose the right plan and device that fits their needs. Receiving and organizing products as they came to the location. Data entry through various forms applications including Excel and Salesforce. Opening and closing duties as well as in charge of cash audits and nightly deposits.



Sales Manager

Cricket Wireless

Dec 2014 - Oct 2015 (11 months)

In charge of a small team in sales atmosphere. Duties such as training and maintaining the store. Daily closing duty and nightly cash deposits

Salesperson

RadioShack

Oct 2013 - Dec 2014 (1 year 3 months)

Helped Customers identify correct equipment to fit their needs. Guided customers in selecting mobile phones and plans that fits their needs

Education



Frankfort High

High school

Skills

basic • closing • data entry • forms • microsoft excel • organizational skills • purchasing • receiving • sales • technical support